Digital Media Department Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; nam_ua395-6; 93.44 GB 67737 Digital Files
  - Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; nam_ua395-6.1; 75.21 GB 56337 Digital Files
    - Healthcare Management: 1/14/03 @ 8:00 AM Desmond Hotel Legislative Update digital, 2003 January 1; nam_ua395-6.1_42; 91.5 MB 66 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/24/03 @ 12:30 PM CC Ballroom Martin Luther King Luncheon / Christopher Edley digital, 2003 March 5; nam_ua395-6.1_43; 16.4 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Chartwells: 2/19/03 @ 11:30 AM CC Cafeteria Food Fair digital, 2003 March 5; nam_ua395-6.1_44; 50.5 MB 38 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 5/2/03 @ 2 PM - 4:30 PM Alumni House Distinguished Professor Lecture and Reception: Eric Block digital, 2003 March 20; nam_ua395-6.1_45; 14.9 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/17/03 @ 9 AM UAB Lobby Avon check presentation digital, 2003 March 24; nam_ua395-6.1_46; 2.2 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/24/03 @ 1 PM Small Fountain CC UAlbany Family Event digital, 2003 April 7; nam_ua395-6.1_47; 64.4 MB 55 Digital Files
    - IROW: 4/9/03 @ 1:30 PM Standish Room / Science Library Bread and Roses Awards digital, 2003 April 8; nam_ua395-6.1_48; 23.0 MB 52 Digital Files
    - Athletics: 5/5/03 @ 5:30 PM RACC Great Dane Awards color print, 2003 April 18; nam_ua395-6.1_49; 29.5 MB 69 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 4/8/03 @ 3:30 PM CC Terrace Lounge plaque presentation: "Don't Walk Alone" digital, 2003 April 23; nam_ua395-6.1_50; 1.9 MB 5 Digital Files
    - Outreach: 4/15/03 @ 12:20 PM WRGB Studios / Sch'dy NY Business Matters taping digital, 2003 April 24; nam_ua395-6.1_51; 4.4 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 5/9/03 @ 3 PM - 5 PM CC Ballroom Awards of Excellence digital, 2003 April 29; nam_ua395-6.1_52; 13.2 MB 47 Digital Files
    - Charwells: 4/26/03 @ 7:30 PM RACC Campaign Event digital, 2003 May 13; nam_ua395-6.1_53; 66.9 MB 34 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 7/24/03 @ 1:30 PM Draper 201 interview with Terrance Thornberry and other authors of Gangs and Delinquency digital, 2003 August 6; nam_ua395-6.1_54; 15.0 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 7/24/03 @ 1:30 PM Draper 201 interview with Terrance Thornberry and other authors of Gangs and Delinquency digital, 2003 August 6; nam_ua395-6.1_55; 15.0 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 7/29/03 @ 10:30 AM podium between Art Museum and CAS press conf: NYS Power Authority and DaimlerChrysler announcing electric cars for UAlbany digital, 2003 August 6; nam_ua395-6.1_56; 54.2 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 7/29/03 @ 10:30 AM podium between Art Museum and CAS press conf: NYS Power Authority and DaimlerChrysler announcing electric cars for UAlbany digital, 2003 August 6; nam_ua395-6.1_57; 54.2 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 7/25/03 @ 7 AM RACC Breakfast with the Giants digital, 2003 August 8; nam_ua395-6.1_58; 24.7 MB 63 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 7/25/03 @ 7 AM RACC Breakfast with the Giants digital, 2003 August 8; nam_ua395-6.1_59; 24.7 MB 63 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 9/5/03 @ 4 - 6 PM Alumni House Susan Phillips/School of Education Development Reception digital, 2003 August 27; nam_ua395-6.1_60; 287.6 MB 114 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 9/18/03 @ 3:30 -4:30 PM Desmond Hotel Ctr. For Women in Gov't - panel discussion w/Madeleine Kunin digital, 2003 September 19; nam_ua395-6.1_61; 104.7 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 9/18/03 @ 3:30 -4:30 PM Desmond Hotel Ctr. For Women in Gov't - panel discussion w/Madeleine Kunin digital, 2003 September 19; nam_ua395-6.1_62; 104.7 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/22/03 @ 12:00 Noon Career Development Center Target Check Presentation digital, 2003 October 15; nam_ua395-6.1_63; 17.2 MB 13 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/22/03 @ 12:00 Noon Career Development Center Target Check Presentation digital, 2003 October 15; nam_ua395-6.1_64; 17.2 MB 13 Digital Files
    - photo session: 11/5/03 @ Noon (Location TBA) Check Presentation: Financial Aid Office / Dennis Tillman, Ellen Sax and Jason Santori, 2003 October 31; nam_ua395-6.1_65; 346.1 MB 181 Digital Files
    - photo session: 10/30/03 @ 11 AM Alumni House Campaign Kickoff / NYC, 2003 October 31; nam_ua395-6.1_66; 346.1 MB 181 Digital Files
    - photo session: 10/30/03 @ 11 AM Alumni House Campaign Kickoff / NYC, 2003 October 31; nam_ua395-6.1_67; 346.1 MB 181 Digital Files
    - photo session: 10/30/03 @ 11 AM Alumni House Campaign Kickoff / NYC, 2003 October 31; nam_ua395-6.1_68; 126.9 MB 87 Digital Files
    - photo session: 10/30/03 @ 11 AM Alumni House Campaign Kickoff / NYC, 2003 October 31; nam_ua395-6.1_69; 113.2 MB 81 Digital Files
    - photo session: 10/30/03 @ 11 AM Alumni House Campaign Kickoff / NYC, 2003 October 31; nam_ua395-6.1_70; 346.1 MB 181 Digital Files
    - photo session: 10/30/03 @ 11 AM Alumni House Campaign Kickoff / NYC, 2003 October 31; nam_ua395-6.1_71; 126.9 MB 87 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 11/20/03 @ 6:30 PM PAC Flutterer Lounge Lydia Davis Reception digital, 2003 November 10; nam_ua395-6.1_72; 194.2 MB 58 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/31/03 @ 2:30 PM Main Library Lobby Don't Walk Alone participants digital, 2003 November 10; nam_ua395-6.1_73; 14.8 MB 10 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 11/20/03 @ 6:30 PM PAC Flutterer Lounge Lydia Davis Reception digital, 2003 November 10; nam_ua395-6.1_74; 194.2 MB 58 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/31/03 @ 2:30 PM Main Library Lobby Don't Walk Alone participants digital, 2003 November 10; nam_ua395-6.1_75; 14.8 MB 10 Digital Files
    - photo session: 11/10/03 @ 11 AM Science Library Atrium Press Conf.: Technology Plays Reading, 2003 November 11; nam_ua395-6.1_76; 75.1 MB 92 Digital Files
    - photo session: 11/10/03 @ 11 AM Science Library Atrium Press Conf.: Technology Plays Reading, 2003 November 11; nam_ua395-6.1_77; 109.1 MB 86 Digital Files
    - E2TAC: 11/21/03 @ 8:15 AM CESTM Tech Valley Energy Forum digital, 2003 November 20; nam_ua395-6.1_78; 78.2 MB 26 Digital Files
    - E2TAC: 11/21/03 @ 8:15 AM CESTM Tech Valley Energy Forum digital, 2003 November 20; nam_ua395-6.1_79; 78.2 MB 26 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 12/5/03 @ 2 PM Waterbury Hall Flag Presentation w/ Andre Williams digital, 2003 November 24; nam_ua395-6.1_80; 49.0 MB 23 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 12/5/03 @ 2 PM Waterbury Hall Flag Presentation w/ Andre Williams digital, 2003 November 24; nam_ua395-6.1_81; 49.0 MB 23 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 11/10/03 @ 11 AM Science Library Atrium Press Conf.: Technology Plays Reading digital, 2003 November 24; nam_ua395-6.1_82; 68.2 MB 59 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 11/10/03 @ 11 AM Science Library Atrium Press Conf.: Technology Plays Reading digital, 2003 November 24; nam_ua395-6.1_83; 68.2 MB 59 Digital Files
    - Health Management: 11/19/03 @ 9:30 AM Alumni House Business Seminar digital, 2003 December 2; nam_ua395-6.1_84; 61.9 MB 18 Digital Files
    - Health Management: 11/19/03 @ 9:30 AM Alumni House Business Seminar digital, 2003 December 2; nam_ua395-6.1_85; 61.9 MB 18 Digital Files
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day Event, 2004 January 23; nam_ua395-6.1_86; 125.6 MB 87 Digital Files
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day Event, 2004 January 23; nam_ua395-6.1_87; 54.9 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day Event, 2004 January 23; nam_ua395-6.1_88; 125.6 MB 87 Digital Files
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day Event, 2004 January 23; nam_ua395-6.1_89; 54.9 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Center for Technology and Government: photo session: 1/28/04 @ 3:45 PM 187 Wolf Rd. Albany (next to Marriott Hotel) open house, 2004 January 29; nam_ua395-6.1_90; 125.3 MB 94 Digital Files
    - Center for Technology and Government: photo session: 1/28/04 @ 3:45 PM 187 Wolf Rd. Albany (next to Marriott Hotel) open house, 2004 January 29; nam_ua395-6.1_91; 39.5 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Center for Technology and Government: photo session: 1/28/04 @ 3:45 PM 187 Wolf Rd. Albany (next to Marriott Hotel) open house, 2004 January 29; nam_ua395-6.1_92; 125.3 MB 94 Digital Files
    - Center for Technology and Government: photo session: 1/28/04 @ 3:45 PM 187 Wolf Rd. Albany (next to Marriott Hotel) open house, 2004 January 29; nam_ua395-6.1_93; 39.5 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 2/12/04 @ 12 Noon CC Ballroom 2003 Employee Recognition Luncheon digital, 2004 February 9; nam_ua395-6.1_94; 63.2 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 2/12/04 @ 12 Noon CC Ballroom 2003 Employee Recognition Luncheon digital, 2004 February 9; nam_ua395-6.1_95; 63.2 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Chartwells: photo session: 2/19/03 @ 11:30 AM CC Cafeteria Food Fair, 2004 February 11; nam_ua395-6.1_96; 104.6 MB 67 Digital Files
    - Chartwells: photo session: 2/19/03 @ 11:30 AM CC Cafeteria Food Fair, 2004 February 11; nam_ua395-6.1_97; 69.8 MB 44 Digital Files
    - Chartwells: photo session: 2/10/04 @ 11:45 AM - 12:45 PM CC Cafeteria Annual Food Show; "Taste of Albany", 2004 February 11; nam_ua395-6.1_98; 69.8 MB 44 Digital Files
    - Chartwells: photo session: 2/10/04 @ 11:45 AM - 12:45 PM CC Cafeteria Annual Food Show; "Taste of Albany", 2004 February 11; nam_ua395-6.1_99; 104.6 MB 67 Digital Files
    - Library: 5/21/04 @ 2 PM - 4PM Standish Room Bread and Roses '04 digital, 2004 February 26; nam_ua395-6.1_100; 160.7 MB 107 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/2/04 @ 11 AM CC Ballroom Job Fair digital, 2004 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_101; 45.7 MB 29 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/2/04 @ 11 AM CC Ballroom Job Fair digital, 2004 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_102; 45.7 MB 29 Digital Files
    - Small Business Development Assoc.: 3/11/04 @ 2 PM Waterford and Defreestville environmental portraiture: Ursula Switzerland and Karen Hardken digital, 2004 March 18; nam_ua395-6.1_103; 127.8 MB 89 Digital Files
    - Small Business Development Assoc.: 3/11/04 @ 2 PM Waterford and Defreestville environmental portraiture: Ursula Switzerland and Karen Hardken digital, 2004 March 18; nam_ua395-6.1_104; 127.8 MB 89 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 4/30/04 @ 2:00 PM East Campus Ed Hannan; Distinguished Professor Lecture digital, 2004 March 24; nam_ua395-6.1_105; 73.9 MB 57 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 4/30/04 @ 2:00 PM East Campus Ed Hannan; Distinguished Professor Lecture digital, 2004 March 24; nam_ua395-6.1_106; 73.9 MB 57 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 3/12/04 @ 11 AM CC Ballroom Welcome for Interm President John Ryan digital, 2004 March 26; nam_ua395-6.1_107; 142.1 MB 90 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 3/12/04 @ 11 AM CC Ballroom Welcome for Interm President John Ryan digital, 2004 March 26; nam_ua395-6.1_108; 142.1 MB 90 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/30/04 @ 10:30 AM Parent's Fountain Courtyard Storm Ready Plaque Unveiling digital, 2004 May 14; nam_ua395-6.1_109; 60.8 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/30/04 @ 10:30 AM Parent's Fountain Courtyard Storm Ready Plaque Unveiling digital, 2004 May 14; nam_ua395-6.1_110; 60.8 MB 41 Digital Files
    - Library: photo session: 5/21/04 @ 2 PM - 4PM Standish Room Bread and Roses '04, 2004 May 22; nam_ua395-6.1_111; 133.3 MB 90 Digital Files
    - Library: photo session: 5/21/04 @ 2 PM - 4PM Standish Room Bread and Roses '04, 2004 May 22; nam_ua395-6.1_112; 133.3 MB 90 Digital Files
    - Library: photo session: 5/21/04 @ 2 PM - 4PM Standish Room Bread and Roses '04, 2004 May 22; nam_ua395-6.1_113; 27.4 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Library: photo session: 5/21/04 @ 2 PM - 4PM Standish Room Bread and Roses '04, 2004 May 22; nam_ua395-6.1_114; 27.4 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Diversity and Affirmative Action: A poem that needs to be matted and framed "Visionary Pioneer" by Winsome Foderingham-Williams. A tribute to Karen H. Hitchock., 2004 May 24; nam_ua395-6.1_115; 52.1 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 5/21/04 @ 10:30 AM President's Office Check Presentation w/ Bob Fortune digital, 2004 June 1; nam_ua395-6.1_116; 11.7 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 5/21/04 @ 10:30 AM President's Office Check Presentation w/ Bob Fortune digital, 2004 June 1; nam_ua395-6.1_117; 11.7 MB 8 Digital Files
    - media and marketing: 7/28/04 @ 11:30 AM Dutch Quad Lawn Giant's Media Day '04 digital, 2004 August 11; nam_ua395-6.1_118; 103.4 MB 79 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 7/30/04 @ 7:30 AM RRAC / practice field VIP Breakfast_Giants digital, 2004 August 13; nam_ua395-6.1_119; 160.8 MB 113 Digital Files
    - President: 9/22/04 @ 3:30 PM Hastings-on-Hudson / Riverview Banquet House Jewish Studies Event digital, 2004 August 18; nam_ua395-6.1_120; 218.5 MB 143 Digital Files
    - Outreach: 8/16/04 @ 3 PM 50 Colvin Ave. New School for Broadcasting digital, 2004 August 30; nam_ua395-6.1_121; 44.7 MB 24 Digital Files
    - Outreach: 8/16/04 @ 3 PM 50 Colvin Ave. New School for Broadcasting digital, 2004 August 30; nam_ua395-6.1_122; 44.7 MB 24 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 8/17/04 @ 9 AM Football Field President Ryan w/ Phil McConky digital, 2004 August 31; nam_ua395-6.1_123; 51.3 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Alumni Affairs: 10/9/04 @ 11 AM BA-229 Forbes Classroom Dedication digital, 2004 September 9; nam_ua395-6.1_124; 141.5 MB 106 Digital Files
    - President: 10/6/04 @ 12 noon CC375 Chancellor's Awards Luncheon digital, 2004 September 15; nam_ua395-6.1_125; 70.1 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 11/10/04 @ noon CC Ballroom Employee Recognition Luncheon digital, 2004 September 17; nam_ua395-6.1_126; 54.8 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 10/28/04 @ 3:30 PM Fireside Lounge / CC New Faculty / Staff Reception digital, 2004 October 13; nam_ua395-6.1_127; 39.1 MB 27 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 10/27/04 @ 11 AM - 1 PM Desmond Hotel Paulette McCormick and Pres. Ryan, Senator Bruno / luncheon digital, 2004 October 14; nam_ua395-6.1_128; 94.4 MB 73 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/7/04 @ 9:30 Corporate Woods Albany portrait: John Nigro digital, 2004 October 18; nam_ua395-6.1_129; 38.6 MB 29 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 10/13/04 @ 10:30 AM - 12 Noon Life Science Bldg. Life Science Grand Opening ribbon cutting / reception digital, 2004 October 21; nam_ua395-6.1_130; 147.8 MB 120 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 10/28/04 @ 5:30 PM Desmond Hotel Colonie Business Capital Region Alumni Event digital, 2004 November 10; nam_ua395-6.1_131; 189.0 MB 126 Digital Files
    - Outreach: 11/8/04 @ 11:30 AM U Kids / Dutch Quad students: Ben and Jessie with kids digital, 2004 November 18; nam_ua395-6.1_132; 60.3 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Outreach: 11/8/04 @ 11:30 AM U Kids / Dutch Quad students: Ben and Jessie with kids digital, 2004 November 18; nam_ua395-6.1_133; 60.3 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Outreach: 11/8/04 @ 11:30 AM U Kids / Dutch Quad students: Ben and Jessie with kids digital, 2004 November 18; nam_ua395-6.1_134; 60.3 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Small Business Development Assoc.: Photo session: 11/12/04 @ 2 PM Elizaville, NY portrait: Vanessa Holsapple / Client of the Year digital, 2004 November 19; nam_ua395-6.1_135; 40.4 MB 21 Digital Files
    - President: 12/2 /04 @ 10:30 AM UAB President's Office Check Presentation w/ Key Bank digital, 2004 December 14; nam_ua395-6.1_136; 12.0 MB 8 Digital Files
    - SUNY Central: Photo sessioin: 12/3/04 @ 10:45 CC Ballroom "Town and Gown" Plenary Session digital, 2004 December 17; nam_ua395-6.1_137; 166.9 MB 115 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 5/5/05 @ 5 PM - 10:00 PM Hall of Springs Saratoga Springs, NY Citizen Laureate Dinner '05, 2005 March 15; nam_ua395-6.1_138; 160.8 MB 104 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/21/05 @ Noon Standish Room Lunch with Collins Fellows digital, 2005 April 4; nam_ua395-6.1_139; 29.5 MB 20 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/29/05 @ Noon Patroon Room Student Leaders Lunch digital, 2005 April 12; nam_ua395-6.1_140; 11.3 MB 7 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 4/5/05 @ 10 AM UAB Lobby Key Bank Check Presentation with Ellen Sax, Cathy Lowery and Carol Bullard digital, 2005 April 13; nam_ua395-6.1_141; 12.0 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Special Events: 4/25/05 @ various times Life Sciences Bldg Nobel Laureate: Elias J. Corey 1:15 PM Meeting with Students and Faculy 2:45 PM - Convocation 3:45 PM - Reception 4:30 PM - Lecture digital, 2005 April 19; nam_ua395-6.1_142; 154.1 MB 107 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/12/05 @ Noon Draper Cafeteria Rockefeller Policy Lunch digital, 2005 April 25; nam_ua395-6.1_143; 55.1 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/13/05 @ 2 PM Location TBA Research Colloquium digital, 2005 April 25; nam_ua395-6.1_144; 68.2 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/17/05 @ 11 AM - 4 PM Collins Circle/Fountain Fountain Day 2005 digital, 2005 May 2; nam_ua395-6.1_145; 629.0 MB 269 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/25/05 @ 11 AM ASCUS LI36 Advisement Services Tour digital, 2005 May 6; nam_ua395-6.1_146; 32.1 MB 23 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/26/05 @ Noon Desmond Hotel Tech Valley Summit digital, 2005 May 6; nam_ua395-6.1_147; 83.0 MB 51 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/27/05 8:30 AM - 4:30 PM Various locations President for a Day / Richard Nichols II digital, 2005 May 6; nam_ua395-6.1_148; 11.5 MB 8 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/28/05 @ 8:45 AM CC Assembly Hall Welcome / Dr. William Harvey and James Anderson / Diversity Presentations digital, 2005 May 6; nam_ua395-6.1_149; 41.2 MB 28 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/7/05 @ 9:30 AM Lutheran Church / Albany 181 Western ave. Pancake Breakfast digital, 2005 May 23; nam_ua395-6.1_150; 198.6 MB 112 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/11/05 @ noon Federal Bldg / 3 rd fl courtroom (Broadway and State St. Albany, NY) Roundtable Luncheon digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-6.1_151; 105.9 MB 66 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3 PM University Library / 1 st floor reading and book signing w_KLH digital, 2005 May 24; nam_ua395-6.1_152; 48.1 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/12/05 @ 10 AM City Hall / Mayor's Conference Room Midtown Colleges Meeting digital, 2005 May 26; nam_ua395-6.1_153; 67.1 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/17/05 @ 11:30 AM CC Terrace Lounge GSO lunch meeting digital, 2005 May 27; nam_ua395-6.1_154; 90.2 MB 56 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/17/05 @ 11:30 AM CC Terrace Lounge GSO lunch meeting digital, 2005 May 27; nam_ua395-6.1_155; 90.2 MB 56 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/17/05 @ 11:30 AM CC Terrace Lounge GSO lunch meeting digital, 2005 May 27; nam_ua395-6.1_156; 90.2 MB 56 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/25/05 @ 3:30 PM Hall of Fame Room / RACC Digital Youth Graduation digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_157; 106.0 MB 71 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/26/05 @ 7:30 AM Marriott Hotel Wolf Rd. Pancake Breakfast for Healthcare digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_158; 237.9 MB 93 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/26/05 @ 10:30 AM SUNY Tunes tour of recording facility digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_159; 85.7 MB 56 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/26/05 @ 2 PM Standish Room Ctr for Elimination of Minority Health Disparities digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_160; 198.9 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/25/05 @ 3:30 PM Hall of Fame Room / RACC Digital Youth Graduation digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_161; 106.0 MB 71 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/26/05 @ 7:30 AM Marriott Hotel Wolf Rd. Pancake Breakfast for Healthcare digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_162; 237.9 MB 93 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/26/05 @ 10:30 AM SUNY Tunes tour of recording facility digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_163; 85.7 MB 56 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/26/05 @ 2 PM Standish Room Ctr for Elimination of Minority Health Disparities digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_164; 198.9 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/25/05 @ 3:30 PM Hall of Fame Room / RACC Digital Youth Graduation digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_165; 106.0 MB 71 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/26/05 @ 7:30 AM Marriott Hotel Wolf Rd. Pancake Breakfast for Healthcare digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_166; 237.9 MB 93 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/26/05 @ 10:30 AM SUNY Tunes tour of recording facility digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_167; 85.7 MB 56 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/26/05 @ 2 PM Standish Room Ctr for Elimination of Minority Health Disparities digital, 2005 June 6; nam_ua395-6.1_168; 198.9 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Advancement Events: 6/3/05 @ 7:30 AM Desmond Hotel Latham, NY Council for Economic Outreach Breakfast digital, 2005 June 9; nam_ua395-6.1_169; 114.7 MB 78 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 6/14/05 @ 7:30 AM location TBA Public Affairs Roundtable digital, 2005 June 21; nam_ua395-6.1_170; 140.0 MB 86 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 6/16/05 @ time and location TBA NERFI DNA Academy / ribbon cutting digital, 2005 June 21; nam_ua395-6.1_171; 207.9 MB 123 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 6/13/05 @ 3:30 pm Standish Room Chancellor's Regional Meeting with Presidents digital, 2005 June 21; nam_ua395-6.1_172; 103.2 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 7/20/05 @ 5 PM - 6:30 PM Prez Rez IFW Garden Reception digital, 2005 June 22; nam_ua395-6.1_173; 186.7 MB 110 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 7/21/05 @ 1 PM - 3 PM Empire Commons Summer Celebration digital, 2005 June 22; nam_ua395-6.1_174; 150.2 MB 122 Digital Files
    - President: 7/8/05 @ 4 PM Community Bldg/Empire Commons "We the People" Seminar / group photo digital, 2005 July 15; nam_ua395-6.1_175; 84.8 MB 52 Digital Files
    - Business: 10/27/05 @ 5:30 - 8 PM Crowne Plaza Times Square, NYC Alumni Networking Event digital, 2005 August 5; nam_ua395-6.1_176; 292.3 MB 78 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 7/28/05 @ 12 Noon Dutch Quad Field Giants Media Day digital, 2005 August 11; nam_ua395-6.1_177; 122.3 MB 85 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 9/9/05 @ 5:30 - 7 PM Pres Res 1844 Club Reception digital, 2005 August 29; nam_ua395-6.1_178; 163.7 MB 106 Digital Files
    - President: 8/24/05 @ Noon - 1 PM CC Patroon Room New Faculty Orientation digital, 2005 September 2; nam_ua395-6.1_179; 60.7 MB 34 Digital Files
    - President: 8/24/05 @ 6:30 PM - 7:30 PM CC Ballroom Welcome Banquet for International Students digital, 2005 September 2; nam_ua395-6.1_180; 61.1 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Sports Infromation: 8/23/05 @ 11 AM Giant's Practice Field Press Conference: new contract digital, 2005 September 6; nam_ua395-6.1_181; 131.6 MB 88 Digital Files
    - President: 9/8/05 @ 1:30 PM Harriman Campus Building 7-A / Suite 200 - 2nd Fl conference rm. Harriman Campus BOD Meeting digital, 2005 September 12; nam_ua395-6.1_182; 31.5 MB 20 Digital Files
    - President: 9/8/05 @ 3 PM Location TBA China Working Group digital, 2005 September 12; nam_ua395-6.1_183; 24.8 MB 18 Digital Files
    - President: 9/9/05 @ 10:00 AM Grenander Archive Room / Science Library CSEA Archives Photo op digital, 2005 September 12; nam_ua395-6.1_184; 85.2 MB 54 Digital Files
    - Development Events: 10/17/05 @ 6 PM - 8 PM GenNY Sis Research Ctr East Campus private dinner digital, 2005 September 15; nam_ua395-6.1_185; 23.4 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Development Events: 10/18/05 @ 9:45 AM - Noon GenNYSis East Campus ribbon cutting digital, 2005 September 15; nam_ua395-6.1_186; 184.2 MB 126 Digital Files
    - President: 9/13/05 @ 4:15 PM PAC Recital Hall Constitution Day / Pres Hall's History Class digital, 2005 September 22; nam_ua395-6.1_187; 59.1 MB 37 Digital Files
    - President: 9/12/05 @ 11:00 AM Standish Room Press conference digital, 2005 September 22; nam_ua395-6.1_188; 229.2 MB 150 Digital Files